Z/A Zakria **Ahmed**

OBJECTIVE

Junior Web Developer with 3 plus years of experience able to build net applications from the ground up-information gathering, planning design, development, testing and delivery and maintenance. Extremely passionate towards software architecture and design combined with sensitivity to serve the needs of the business balanced with the delivery of high quality solutions.



ADDRESS Rawalpindi Pakistan



PHONE 03427621976



EMAIL

EXPERIENCE

Jan 2019 - Feb 2020

Web Developer, Self Employed

- Custom pages
- Wordpress themes

April 2020 - March 2021

Web and Mobile Application Development

- Custom web applications
- Facebook (prize game) applications

April 2021 - December 2021

Junior Web Developer

Various Companies

- Website development
- Custom pages
- Web application development
- Custom applications

EDUCATION

Fauji Foundation School, Rawalpindi (Matriculation)

Concepts College, Rawalpindi (Intermediate)

COMMUNICATION

- Urdu
- English

SKILLS

- Computer proficiency Communication skills
- Problem-solving abilities
- Html
- Css
- Javascript
- Ethical Hacking

Hobbies

- Reading
- GardeningPhotography